{
  "shortDescription": "Test your knowledge of famous movie quotes with this quiz.",
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "Who said, 'I'll be back'?",
      "answers": ["Terminator", "Rambo", "Rocky"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Who said, 'Here's looking at you, kid'?",
      "answers": ["Rick", "Sam", "Victor"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Who said, 'May the Force be with you'?",
      "answers": ["Obi-Wan", "Han", "Luke"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Who said, 'I am your father'?",
      "answers": ["Vader", "Yoda", "Leia"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Who said, 'You talking to me?'",
      "answers": ["Travis", "Rocky", "Terminator"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Who said, 'Houston, we have a problem'?",
      "answers": ["Lovell", "Armstrong", "Glenn"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Who said, 'I'll have what she's having'?",
      "answers": ["Sally", "Harry", "Customer"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "Who said, 'To infinity and beyond'?",
      "answers": ["Buzz", "Woody", "Andy"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Who said, 'Just keep swimming'?",
      "answers": ["Dory", "Nemo", "Marlin"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Who said, 'Why so serious?'",
      "answers": ["Joker", "Batman", "Harvey"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Who said, 'Elementary, my dear Watson'?",
      "answers": ["Holmes", "Poirot", "Marlowe"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Who said, 'I see dead people'?",
      "answers": ["Cole", "Bruce", "David"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    }
  ]
}
